1. Code Layout:
   ò	Indentation: Use 4 spaces per indentation level.
   ò	Maximum Line Length: 115 characters
   ò	Blank Lines: Use blank lines to separate functions, classes, and blocks of code within functions.
   ò	Using Black (Hotkey ^K^D) to beautify the code.

2. Naming Conventions:
   ò	Variables and Functions: snake_case.
   ò	Classes: PascalCase (CamelCase).
   ò	Enums and their members: PascalCase (CamelCase).
   ò	Constants: UPPER_CASE_WITH_UNDERSCORES.
   ò	Abstract classes start with an I as Interface.
   ò	class-internal (local) methods, properties and variables start with an underscore.
   ò	boolean variables start with "is" or "has".

3. Imports:
   ò	Place imports at the top of the file.
   ò	Group imports into three categories:
   1.	Standard library imports.
   2.	Third-party library imports.
   3.	Local application/library imports.

4. Whitespace:
   ò	Avoid extraneous whitespace in expressions and statements.
   ò	Use a single space around operators and after commas but not inside parentheses.

5. Comments:
   ò	Write comments that are clear, concise, and relevant.
   ò	Use docstrings for documenting public modules, classes, and functions.

6. String Quotes:
   ò	Use double quotes consistently within a project.

7. Exceptions:
   ò	Use try-except blocks for handling exceptions.

8. Miscellaneous:
   ò	Use descriptive variable names.
   ò	Avoid mutable default arguments in functions.
   ò	Type checking in Visual Studio must be set to "strict" (Options/Python/Analysis)

9. Use a Python virtual environment named "env" and use the requirements.txt file to install the required packages.
   "env" is git-ignored.


